Infuriating...
Absolutely vexing!
Your Majesty?
You're covered in dirt!
What happened?
Moreover, where are all the others?
Those damned incompetents!
Why do I bother giving them such
high-caliber weaponry
if they can't even use it properly?!
Your Majesty...
What in the world could that be?
Th-this can't be real...
It's the Dragon of Calamity...
But how?
The Brionac should have killed it!
Don't tell me...
It got resurrected?
That sort of thing
shouldn't be possible...
But they have that one bastard.
A diabolical man that can use
healing magic far beyond anyone else...
Sain!
Wait, even if he did heal it,
it's impossible for them
to just sic that dragon on me.
Which means someone is controlling it...
Demonfolk?
Where is that man?!
Pardon?
That one beast tamer!
Do you mean Master Lude?
He's already left for Sarenza.
It seems there's urgent business
that requires his attention.
That damned sly dog...
Changed sides, has he?!
Why didn't you detain him?!
Y-Your Majesty, you told us
to give him special treatment, so...
Your Majesty, please compose yourself!
Why don't you stop
standing around like an ass
and come up with a plan to fix this?!
Damned good-for-nothings!
As you wish.
Hey! Get the device ready!
Huh? Which device do you mean?
The Keraunos!
Keraunos?!
Hurry it up!
W-with all due respect,
that weapon is still in the testing stage.
The power output remains too high,
and the sights haven't finished
being properly aligned.
On top of that,
it's dangerous to use in the city!
You pathetic fools!
Do you not see the disaster
that's right in front of your eyes?
B-but, even so, the possibility of
collateral damage is very real-
Do it.
We just need one shot.
That's all it will take to kill it.
If you can't aim it properly,
then just implement Mana Tracing
on the gun barrel.
Yes, Your Majesty, as you command!
Pitiful dragon.
I'm going to blow you away
without a single trace this time.
Acquiring target.
Direction: 1120.
Angle of fire: 40 degrees.
Mana tracing applied.
This is the greatest technological
wonder in the empire,
developed under the wise leadership
of Deridas the Third:
The light of judgement!
Parry!
Wh-what's going on?
The trajectory of Keraunos changed
and now it's raining down on us!
What could have caused that?!
B-because it was set to trace mana!
Our mana furnaces
have become its new target!
Who authorized using that setting?!
You imbeciles!
We're all done for.
Ugh! I can't deal with
this mess any longer!
You're in charge of handling the rest!
That's an order from your direct superior!
W-wait!
You, Aide, do something!
That's an order
from your direct superior!
It's been a pleasure, sir!
You bastards!
I'll have your heads for this!
S-stop...
Please stop...
Don't hit those...
Anywhere but those!
M-make it stop...
I'm sorry, I've lost track of him.
I'm trying to seek out his location,
but it's as if there's a thick wall
preventing me from doing so.
Sounds like he took refuge
in a building made of mana metal.
Instructor Noor...
Something's heading this way.
It's magnitudes stronger
than that light from before!
Dodge it!
There's not enough time!
Everyone, get behind me!
Instructor Noor!
Parry!
Thank goodness...
Instructor!
What do you think you're doing?!
You were the one who ordered me to come up
with a way to fix this, Your Majesty.
Bastards!
You must realize this is treason
against the crown!
But it's also the only way we can ensure
the empire survives!
S-stop it...
H-help! Someone!
There is no one here
who is still willing to obey you.
Say your prayers.
Phew. What a stroke of luck.
Hm? The sparkly gold old man...
Who the hell are you?!
Do you mean to protect this man?
Uh, no?
Then stay out of our way!
I'm not sure what's happening,
but calm down.
Parry!
Old man, get down!
What are you attacking me for?
This guy's a skilled bodyguard.
We all have to charge him together!
Wait, this is a misunderstanding!
I don't see any other way
to interpret this situation!
Parry!
That man has brought irreparable harm
upon our country!
And he must atone for it with his life!
I don't know what's going on,
but can't you just talk this out or something?
Were that possible,
we'd have done it long ago!
Is that a bomb?!
Watch out!
Oops.
Why are you ganging up on him like this?!
He's just an old man, you know?!
Hold on, you're the one
who sent him flying.
I mean, isn't this guy supposed
to be your emperor?
I can't make heads or tails
of this situation.
You don't need to understand!
Oh no!
Cut it out already!
What is your deal?!
Are you just trying to kill him yourself?!
No, of course not!
He's old enough to kick
the bucket any day now.
Why not let nature take its course?
Because we don't have
a single moment to spare!
The enemy is already
invading our territory!
And they've got that
Dragon of Calamity in tow!
Invading?
That's precisely why we need to show them
we have no intention of fighting!
Our country is doomed
unless we offer them this man's head!
It's for our survival!
Wait right there.
We appreciate your thoughtfulness,
but there will be no need for all of that.
Dead men cannot atone
for their crimes, after all.
You guys made it. What a relief.
Instructor, I'm glad you're safe.
Yeah.
I thought I was gonna die,
but I got lucky.
Are these people who I think they are?
Yes.
Sir Noor.
Will you let us take care
of everything from here on?
Sure, I think the safest way to handle this
is to negotiate rather than fight.
And it doesn't seem like
they'll listen to me.
I am in your debt.
Lynne, could you go with Sir Noor
and tend to his wounds?
Let's go, Instructor Noor.
Okay. Good luck sorting this out.
Now then...
It's been a while since our
last encounter, Circuit of Ten.
Prince Rein...
Please lower your swords, gentlemen.
Before anything else,
we'd like to talk to that man.
Help... Spare me...
Spare you?
Are you saying that you want forgiveness?
Yes, of course I intend to forgive you.
R-really? Then I-
There are currently 23 people
in our nation who have gone missing.
What?
Nineteen people have been buried
under crumbling homes.
Thirteen people that have
burned to death in fires.
Thirty-eight people
injured by falling debris.
Furthermore,
the people who were torn apart, crushed,
and reduced to mangled pieces of flesh
by the beasts you
unleashed in the city!
There are 127 of those.
That's the total number of casualties
in my country.
Although, I'm sure there are more
we don't know about.
Wh-why are you telling me this?
Just as I said earlier,
I will forgive you.
That is, only if you're willing to
experience the same amount of suffering
as all those I just mentioned.
Once that's finished,
I would like to hold a multinational talk
about reparations and ending the war.
Do I hear any objections to this proposal?
No objections!
W-wait!
What in the world do you mean by...
the same amount of suffering?
No need to worry.
You'll experience the same,
but you won't die.
Even if we break off your legs
and crush your innards,
I shall make sure you are
healed enough by the end
to at least participate in the talks.
H-help me...
Even if you can't tolerate the suffering
and you lose consciousness,
I'll bring you back.
And you can cry and scream
as much as you'd like.
P-please, spare me!
Don't get me wrong.
We aren't doing this
because we want to.
What we want is for you
to thoroughly understand
the pain you put our people through.
That's all it's going to cost you
for forgiveness.
Our nation is incredibly merciful...
don't you think?
Thanks.
I feel much better.
Glad to hear that, Instructor.
All this damage...
Did that light from earlier cause it?
That's right.
The powerful mana beam
that you deflected got split,
and rained down on the imperial capital.
Oh, damn. I did something awful...
Don't let it bother you.
You did it to protect us, Instructor.
That may be true, but...
Someone must have died, right?
You don't have to worry about that.
Apparently, the facilities that got destroyed
were all mana furnaces.
Mana furnaces?
Yes.
Those areas have a very high
concentration with mana,
so people can't even enter them.
Oh, yeah?
Then that's good.
Of course, it will affect the lives
of the citizens here,
but not as much as the people
of our nation.
Brother!
Then it's all over now, right?
Yeah.
From here on, both our countries
are moving towards
coordinating post-war reconstruction.
The war barely started
and now it's already over?
Then I don't get why we just
didn't talk it out from the beginning.
So, what about the old man?
The emperor?
He chose to abdicate the throne.
And it's likely his grandchild
will be chosen to inherit the crown next.
His grandchild, huh?
They're only 10 years old at this point.
Which means that a guardian
has to be appointed.
It will be the Circuit of Ten
you met earlier.
Those ten guys, huh?
Sir Noor? Do I have your name right?
Yeah.
Sorry about earlier.
I'd like to apologize for
misunderstanding the situation
and turning our blades on you.
I will do whatever it takes
to make amends.
I'm not really worried about it,
so you don't need to make amends.
More importantly, you need to reconsider
your morals if you think it's okay
to gang up on the elderly like that.
Right, I know it is something
I should be ashamed of.
Had you not been there to stop us,
our empire would have ended up
in a very nasty civil war.
I'd like to thank you, wholeheartedly.
No, I really don't deserve your thanks...
It's more like I was the one
who got saved, you know?
Huh?
I thought I was done for
when I leapt off the dragon's back,
but luckily, you guys had a floor
for me to land safely on.
Lucky to land safely on the floor?
You truly are an amusing man!
Okay, let's leave it at that, then.
But don't forget:
In the future, we will spare
no expense to assist you.
So if you ever need our help, let me know.
We will risk our lives
to come to your aid.
Wow, that's dramatic.
I'll be okay.
Don't hesitate to ask.
Anyways, I'm sorry I damaged
your city so badly.
Instructor Noor...
There's no need
to concern yourself with that.
As of right now,
there are no reports of dead or injured.
The crimes of our country,
which threw away the treaty
and attacked your nation,
are far more serious.
But tell me if there's anything
I can do for you.
I can at least help get rid of the rubble.
Really?
You're a good-hearted person,
almost to a fault.
It says it's bored and wants to go home.
Well, please excuse us.
From here on out,
we'll correspond through messengers.
Yes, please return home safely.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Sir Noor!
My apologies for not giving my name.
I am the imperial sorcerer Randeus,
of the Circuit of Ten.
Okay.
Ran... Randeus, right?
I'll remember.
Maybe.
I do look forward
to seeing you again someday.
Yeah, I'll see ya around.
Okay. We're taking off.
Rolo, will you ask it something?
On the way home,
can we fly closer to the ground?
Okay, I'll ask.
Instructor Noor...
I can tell he's deeply concerned
about the damage done to this nation.
What a compassionate person he is.
I must learn from his example!
We've all returned safely.
The war is now over.
Sorry to make you do
all the negotiating, Rein.
You can fill me in on the details later.
Before that, I must extend thanks
to our savior.
Yes.
Sir Noor made incredible
contributions on the battlefield.
He needs a reward worthy of his deeds.
Reward? No, I don't want one.
What?
I'm flattered, but I'm not really
in need of anything.
No, no.
You can't just refuse this time.
I need to provide you
with a proper reward,
or else it will set a bad example.
I get that, but...
Man, this family really
wants to push stuff on you
even if you say
you don't want anything.
Actually, there is one thing
I want to ask for.
O-oh? Ah, I see!
Go ahead, just name it.
Well, I would like you
to help this kid out.
Uh, what? Me?
This child is demonfolk, correct?
Yes.
Seems he doesn't have anyone to live with.
Since he was abandoned
by a group of merchants.
Then what is your request?
I want you to let him live in the capital.
And provide him with a normal life,
just like all the other citizens.
I considered us living together,
but it's better for him to be looked after
by a rich family,
and not someone with
an unsteady income, like me.
Instructor Noor...
You said you'd give me a house
and land before, right?
Something like that would be fine.
And some clothes and food
would be good, if you can.
All right.
But for that to happen, this boy will
need to become a citizen of this kingdom.
Is that what you wish?
He's saved me countless times.
The only reason that huge dragon
did what I said was because he was with me.
No, it was because you-
No need to be humble.
If Rolo weren't there, the war wouldn't
have ended so quickly.
That's all I want.
Of all the things he could ask for...
The Holy Theocracy of Mithra
regards the demonfolk as enemies,
which means accepting one in our kingdom
will cause a rift in
the relations between us.
Just so you know...
I don't need anything aside from that.
If you want to give me other rewards,
then spend them elsewhere instead.
There is no shortage of people
who've lost their homes.
And that's really
where you should be focusing
all your resources on right now, isn't it?
That is true...
As a matter of fact,
you're absolutely right.
This guy really likes to laugh, huh?
If I'm reborn, I hope I won't
get beaten so badly in my next life.
I hope I can be at least
a little bit useful to someone.
And I hope I can have something
delicious to eat, at least once.
For the time being,
you will be living here together with me.
So, welcome home, Rolo.
What's wrong?
They prepared a nice meal for us,
but it'll get cold
if you don't hurry and eat.
Huh?
I can eat this?
Of course you can.
This is our dinner.
Or is there something here
you don't like?
This is... real food?
Come now, don't be shy.
No one will be angry with you
no matter what you eat.
Have as much as you want.
Okay then...
Thanks for the... food.
It's... soft?
What's the matter?
It's... delicious.
Slow down, no one will
take it from you, okay?
Yeah.
#11 I Parry Divine Wrath